let us now speak about backward
现在让我们谈论倒退
induction and backward induction can be
感应和向后感应都可以
viewed as a way of computing the
被视为一种计算
sub-game perfect equilibrium of a game
子游戏的游戏完美平衡
it's a procedure that used widely or
这个程序被广泛使用
variants of it are used widely in game
它的变体在游戏中被广泛使用
playing programs be it chess or other
下棋或其他棋子的程序
ones and and how does this work so this
一个，以及它是如何工作的，所以这个
is a busy busy slide and don't be
是忙碌的幻灯片，不要
daunted we'll explain it
令人畏惧的我们会解释
leisurely also the some of you may have
你们中的一些人也悠闲地
not seen algorithms before but we'll
以前没有看过算法，但我们会
explain the algorithm in very plain
很简单地解释算法
terms before we do let's just first give
我们开始之前先给我们一些条件
the intuition and the intuition is very
直觉和直觉非常
straightforward what we're trying to do
直截了当我们要做什么
is associate a value of the game not
关联游戏的价值而不是
only with leaf nodes with leaf nodes we
只有叶节点和叶节点
know what the value is it's simply
知道它的价值是什么
defined by the payoff vector associated
由相关的收益向量定义
with the leaf node it's part of the game
叶子节点是游戏的一部分
definition but suppose we want to go to
定义，但假设我们要转到
the root of the node or any other
节点的根或任何其他根
internal node and say so what really is
内部节点，然后说真的
the payoff associated here assuming that
假设这里的收益相关
agent will play a sub game perfect
代理会完美玩一个子游戏
equilibrium and that's the goal of this
平衡，这就是这个目标
procedure called backward induction and
称为反向归纳和
the tuition is very straightforward
学费很简单
we'll go to the leaves and back up
我们会去树叶后退
slowly if at every step of the of the
如果在
way assuming the agent will maximize
假设代理将最大化的方式
take an action then maximize their
采取行动，然后尽最大努力
payoff at that node and so that's the
在那个节点上的回报，这就是
intuition now let's see how it's done
直觉现在让我们看看它是如何完成的
formally the procedure is called
正式的程序称为
backward induction and it takes one
向后感应，需要一个
argument a node a node in a tree
将一个节点作为树中的一个节点
any node it could be the root could be a
它可能是根的任何节点都可以是
leaf or anything in between and of
叶子或之间的任何东西
course every node has some player
当然每个节点都有一些玩家
associated with it and just anticipate
与它相关联并只是预期
what will encounter shortly row of H
不久将遇到H行
will be the player so that with that
将成为玩家，因此
node H and when the procedure returns
节点H以及过程返回时
will give us those payoffs as payoffs of
会将这些收益作为我们的收益
us to all of the agents associated with
我们与所有相关的代理商
that node so how did that work and again
该节点，那么它又如何工作
remembering to remain
记得留下来
our intuition we say the following if H
我们的直觉，如果H
is the leaf node Z is a set of leaf
是叶节点Z是一组叶
nodes if H is a leaf node then we simply
如果H是叶节点，那么我们简单地
return the payoff vector as defined by
返回由定义的收益向量
the game that's where the recursion
递归的游戏
bottoms out most of the work of course
当然会使大多数工作触底
happens in the recursive step when we're
发生在递归步骤中
not at the leaf node so for that we do
不是在叶节点上，为此
the following we will keep a variable
接下来我们将保留一个变量
called bess util and best util will be a
称为bess util，最好的util将是
vector a vector of path associated with
向量与路径相关的向量
the agents each one one one with each
代理商各一一
agents and we will be updating that that
代理商，我们将对此进行更新
that vector as we as we go along so to
沿着我们前进的那个向量
start out with will assume that payoffs
开始时将假设收益
are all terrible let's call that minus
都是可怕的，我们称之为负号
infinity a payoff smaller than all
无限远小于所有
possible payoffs in the game and then we
游戏中可能的收益，然后我们
do the following we will look at all the
执行以下操作，我们将查看所有
actions available at that node so Chi of
该节点上的可用动作，因此
H is a set of all actions available at
H是在以下位置可用的所有动作的集合
that node a would be an example of such
该节点a将是这样的一个例子
an action
一种行为
so we'll take each action in turn one at
因此，我们将依次执行每个操作
a time and do the following we will look
一段时间，做下面的事情，我们将看
at the child you reach by taking action
对您采取行动所达到的孩子
a at that node H
在那个节点H
that's called Sigma H away so Sigma
那叫西格玛H所以西格玛
ratio is simply another node one of the
比率只是另一个节点之一
children of node H that you arrive at by
您到达的节点H的子节点
taking that particular action a and
采取特定的行动
we'll recursively look at that vector
我们将递归查看该向量
associated with that child and we will
与那个孩子相关联，我们将
keep it at that very at this variable
保持在这个变量上
called util at child so we have two two
在孩子身上叫util，所以我们有两个两个
vectors notice best util and utilit best
矢量注意最佳效用和最佳效用
utility is the best we found so far this
实用程序是迄今为止我们发现的最好的
for a particular agent and utility is
对于特定的代理和实用程序是
what we found at a try it at a
我们尝试一下发现的
particular child will be go over bingo
特定的孩子将经过宾果游戏
will be going over all the children one
将遍及所有孩子
and if ever the util at trial is better
如果试用的util更好
for the agent then the best util so far
对于代理，那么迄今为止最好的工具
we'll update the best Utah that's what's
我们将更新最好的犹他州
going on here
继续在这里
so this is what this is it says utila
这就是它所说的utila
trial is a vector so look at the element
试用是一个向量，所以看一下元素
of that vector corresponding to the
该向量对应于
agent we care about the agent and note H
代理我们关心代理并注意H
if the utility aisle is better for that
如果公用设施过道对此更好
agent given the best util what we found
代理给了我们最好的效用
so far
至今
then simply updated update based util to
然后只需将基于更新的util更新为
be this utility otherwise leave it
是这个实用程序，否则将其保留
unchanged and so in this way we're
保持不变，因此通过这种方式
cycling through all the children and
骑自行车穿越所有孩子，
finding from that agent car that to whom
从那辆特工车中发现谁
node H belong from his point of view
从他的角度来看，节点H属于
which of all the vectors are best and
所有向量中哪一个最好
again the intuition is he will take the
再次直觉是他会采取
action leading to that child and
导致那个孩子的行动
updating that for that that vector
更新那个矢量
accordingly and that's why when we're
因此，这就是为什么当我们
done with returning the best we found so
完成了我们发现的最好结果的归还
far called best util that is the back a
远被称为最佳效用的是背面
backward induction procedure and notice
向后归纳程序和注意事项
that we don't return a strategy just
我们不只是返回战略
return the list of payoffs and in some
返回收益清单，并在一些
sense it's you can think of it as simply
感觉就是你可以简单地想到它
extending the payoff from the nodes to
将收益从节点扩展到
all internal nodes but even though we
所有内部节点，但即使我们
don't explicitly return the equilibrium
不要明确返回平衡
strategy the one that will be something
战略将是某种东西
perfect it's easy to read it off those
完美，很容易将其阅读
numbers because at every node the agent
数字，因为代理在每个节点上
will take the action that leads it to
将采取导致其行动
the nodes a child node with the best
节点是具有最佳子节点的子节点
utility from his point of view so that
从他的角度来看实用
is the sub game perfect that is the
是完美的子游戏，
procedure for reading sub game perfect
子游戏完美阅读程序
equilibria the backward induction and if
均衡后向归纳和
we look at the special case of zero-sum
我们来看零和的特殊情况
game it's simplified a little bit
游戏，它简化了一点
because then there are only two players
因为那时只有两个玩家
and the payoff for one is - a pair of
而一个的回报是-一对
two to the other so really we only need
两个彼此，所以我们只需要
to keep track of one number associated
跟踪一个关联的数字
with each with each node and so there's
与每个节点，所以有
less bookkeeping to be done and
减少簿记工作
furthermore in such zero-sum games and
而且在这种零和游戏中
all win-lose games are are zero-sum game
所有输输赢的游戏都是零和游戏
for example chess there is a way to
例如国际象棋有一种方法
speed up the backward induction
加快向后归纳
procedure by the way in the zero-sum
零和的方式
game we simply call it the minimax
游戏，我们简称为minimax
procedure because we alternate
程序，因为我们交替
minimizing and maximizing the value what
最小化和最大化价值
they want to minimize it the other to
他们想将其最小化
maximize it and in fact there's a way to
最大化它，实际上有一种方法可以
speed up the procedure and we won't go
加快程序，我们不会去
into it here but the intuition is that
在这里，但直觉是
as you're visiting a certain try
在您尝试尝试时
children of a given node you may find
您可能会发现给定节点的子节点
out that at that point there's no no
在那一点上，没有没有
need to explore the remaining children
需要探索剩下的孩子
of that node as we did in the backward
就像我们向后一样
induction procedure because intuitively
归纳程序，因为直观
it won't matter you've already found a
您已经找到一个
value that means that this node that
值，表示该节点
you're examining the parent node will
您正在检查父节点
never be visited and it's called the
永远不会被访问，它被称为
alphabetic alpha beta pruning procedure
字母alpha beta修剪程序
an optimization of the backward
向后优化
induction or the mini math procedure for
归纳法或迷你数学程序
zero-sum games and you are invited to
零和游戏，邀请您参加
explore it elsewhere there's one more
在其他地方探索它
thing I want to say in connection with
我想说的关于
backward induction and in fact the sub
向后归纳，实际上是子
game perfection and there's sort of two
游戏完美，有两种
different things here and they're all
这里有不同的东西，它们都是
keyed off the same example the famous
揭开了同一个例子的名声
example of the centipede game so this
ipe游戏的例子
well-known example you have two players
一个有两个玩家的著名例子
they alternate turns
他们交替轮流
we have player1 moving and then player 2
我们先移动玩家1，再移动玩家2
moving and then play one again and pair
移动然后再次播放并配对
two and so on and so forth but the
两个，依此类推，但
payoffs are constructed in a contrived
收益是人为的
way so that they're gradually increasing
这样他们逐渐增加
and you can imagine it's called the
你可以想象它被称为
centipede because you can imagine rather
because，因为你可以想象
than have only five legs here you'd have
比这里只有五条腿
a hundred they slowly arise so that the
一百他们慢慢地出现，以便
payoffs here are much smaller than the
这里的收益比
payoffs here and indeed very much so if
回报在这里，实际上，如果
you keep going but even though they rise
你继续前进，即使他们上升
they are contrived in a way that lead to
他们被设计成导致
only one sub game perfect equilibrium
只有一个子博弈完美平衡
faith will defect in every place they
信仰会在他们的每个地方都有缺陷
pair people go down in every place here
一对人在这里的每个地方
so the only outcome sub being perfect
所以唯一的结果子是完美的
outcome is this one where the first
结果是这是第一个
player defects immediately goes down
玩家缺陷立即消失
immediately which is of course similar
立即当然是相似的
to the prisoner's dilemma is a little
囚犯的困境有点
counterintuitive because had they only
违反直觉的，因为他们只有
had the good sense to keep going they
有继续前进的良知
would have gettin gotten something in
本来会得到一些东西
the ballpark of this or this both of
这或这两者的球场
which are much better for both in here
在这里对两者都更好
but nonetheless when you examine you see
但是尽管如此，当您检查时看到
that there's only one one once
一次只有一个
what's up being perfect for your beam
最适合您的光束
here and in fact one only one
在这里，实际上只有一个
equilibrium outcome namely this one and
均衡结果即这一和
you can see it by doing again the
您可以通过再次执行
backward induction procedure if the game
向后归纳程序，如果游戏
progressed and in fact reach this node
进步了，实际上到达了这个节点
what would Parowan do well they would go
Parowan会做什么，他们会去
down getting a four rather than a three
下降到四个而不是三个
but player 2 knows this so knowing the
但是玩家2知道这一点，所以知道
player 1 will go down he'd rather go
玩家1会失败，他宁愿去
down because he'd get a 4 rather than a
下降，因为他得到的是4而不是
3 similarly here player 1 knowing that
同样地，这里有3位玩家1
prayer 2 will go down elects to go down
祈祷2将落下，选民落下
here because they would get 3 rather
在这里，因为他们会得到3个
than 2 and so on and this is really the
比2等等，这确实是
backward induction argument so on the
向后归纳论证等等
one hand clearly a clear account of what
一方面清楚地说明了什么
will happen in this game but there are
将会在这个游戏中发生，但是有
two problems one of them
两个问题之一
is sort of simply experimental and
只是简单的实验和
common-sense and the other is more
常识，另一个是更多
theoretical on the pragmatic level this
在实用层面上是理论上的
common sense simply tells you this is
常识只是告诉你这是
not what's going to happen the place
不是那个地方会发生什么
will cooperate for a while until at some
会合作一段时间，直到某个时候
point in fact somebody would go down and
实际上，有人会落下
in the game they know there's so much to
在游戏中，他们知道还有很多
gain by going forward they would if you
通过前进获得收益，如果您
wish take the chance and the city
希望借此机会和这座城市
intuition is borne out repeatedly in
直觉被反复证明
experiments people do cooperate for a
实验人们确实合作
while until in fact eventually they they
而直到实际上最终他们
may defect so that's a problem for
可能会缺陷，所以这是一个问题
theory but there's also a another
理论，但还有另一种
problem that's theoretical in nature so
本质上是理论上的问题
we know that the only sub-game perfect
我们知道唯一的完美子游戏
equilibrium is one where agents defect
平衡是代理缺陷的一种
go down at any point in time now imagine
随时随地下降现在想像
that the game starts and play one goes
游戏开始并进行一次
across does not go down
跨不下去
what does player to do well on the one
玩家在哪方面做得好
hand you could say well yeah the only
你可以说得好耶是唯一的
sub game perfect equilibrium to go down
子游戏完美平衡下降
that should go down because of those
那应该因为那些
losses backward induction argument and
损失向后归纳论证和
we'll tell them that the best thing for
我们会告诉他们，最好的
them is to go down but that same
他们要下去，但同样
argument told them player two that
论点告诉他们第二个球员
player one would have gone down right
玩家一会掉下去
off the bat but they didn't so maybe
脱颖而出，但他们可能并非如此
they won't go down again but what will
他们不会再下降，但会怎样
they do and fundamentally what happens
他们做到了，从根本上发生了什么
here is you have an event of going
这是你要去的事
across that the standard theory tells
标准理论告诉我们的
you will happen with zero probability
你将以零概率发生
how do you condition on an event that
您如何应对某个事件
had a zero probability prior prior
事前事前概率为零
there's a there's a big literature on
有很多关于
this it's a very interesting deep issue
这是一个非常有趣的深层问题
in game theory we will not help to
在博弈论中，我们无济于事
intuit any deeper but it's interesting
深入了解，但这很有趣
to note it
注意